<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?> 
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Articles About Credit Cards - CreditCards.com</title> 
  <link>http://www.creditcards.com/credit-card-articles.php</link> 
  <description>A directory of articles that deal with credit card basics, bad credit &amp; credit repair, credit &amp; account management, low interest &amp; 0% APR credit cards, balance transfer &amp; debt consolidation, reward programs &amp; cash back cards, airline &amp; frequent flyer programs, student credit card education, credit cards for small business, and prepaid &amp; debit cards.</description> 
  <language>en-us</language>
<item>
<title>Cash Back Bonus Credit Card - 5% back on Everyday Purchases</title>
<link>http://www.creditcards.com/cash-back-bonus-credit-card.php</link>
<category>Reward Programs / Cash Back Cards</category>
<description>Overview of the cash back bonus credit card featuring 5% cash back on everyday consumer and small business spending. The latest information on the major card issuers offering 5% cash back rebates with a credit card.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item>
<item><title>Credit Cards 101 - What are Credit Cards?</title>
<link>http://www.creditcards.com/credit-and-credit-cards.php</link>
<category>Credit Card Basics</category>
<description>Overview of credit card basics - credit cards 101; A discussion of how to establish credit, build a credit rating using a student credit card or a prepaid debit card.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item><title>Types of Credit Cards</title>
<link>http://www.creditcards.com/types-of-credit-cards.php</link><category>Credit Card Basics</category><description>An overview of types of credit cards to review before filling out a credit card application including standard credit cards, balance transfer credit cards, low interest credit cards, credit cards with rewards programs &amp; airline miles credit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Compare Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/compare-article.php</link><category>Credit Card Basics</category><description>An overview of how to compare credit cards and credit card offer reward programs. How a low interest credit card with low interest rates vs. a rewards program or cash back would be better.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Choosing the Right Credit Card for You</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/choosing-the-right-credit-card.php</link><category>Credit Card Basics</category><description>Advice on choosing the right credit card, applying for and finding the credit card that is best for you.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tips for Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/credit-cards-tips-article.php</link><category>Credit Card Basics</category><description>General tips for credit cards including treating a credit card like a loan, keeping track of spending and repaying debts on time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deciding which Credit Card is right for you</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Deciding-which-Credit-Card-is-right-for-you.php</link><category>Credit Card Basics</category><description>Overview on deciding which credit card is right for you, including factors such as interest rate, reward programs, banks and issuers such as Visa, MasterCard, Discover and American Express.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Staying Out Of Trouble With Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/staying-out-of-trouble-with-credit-cards.php</link><category>Credit Card Basics</category><description>General credit card tips and advice on how to manage credit cards and credit card expenditures, emphasis that behind the plastic is real money and real debt so credit cards should be used like a 30-day loan.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ's About Credit Cards with Instant Approval</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/FAQs-Instant-Approval-Credit-Cards.php</link><category>Credit Card Basics</category><description>FAQ's about instant approval credit cards and the differences between instant approval, instant credit, instant decision credit card applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>You Have Been Approved for An Instant Approval Credit Card</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Instant-Approval-Credit-Card-Process.php</link><category>Credit Card Basics</category><description>Once you've received instant approval - now what happens, a description of steps involved with applying online, receiving instant approval for credit card application, review of credit and credit score use for issuers of credit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>The American Express Card: Is it Right for You?</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/The-American-Express-Card.php</link><category>Credit Card Basics</category><description>What do you think of when you think of American Express? Do you think of a card only for the wealthy? Or maybe a credit card out of reach for the common person? Actually, American Express offers credit cards for</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glossary of Credit Card Terms</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/credit-cards-glossary.php</link><category>Credit Card Basics</category><description>A glossary of common credit card terms for credit cards like American Express, MasterCard and Visa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ's about Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/credit_cards_faq.php</link><category>Credit Card Basics</category><description>Frequently asked questions regarding advantages of secure and convenient online credit card applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Brief History of Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/history-of-credit-cards.php</link><category>Credit Card Basics</category><description>History of credit cards including the first general use credit card and the first charge card from American Express and later versions that allowed people to pay over time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Have Bad Credit and Need a Credit Card?</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Have-Bad-Credit-and-Need-a-Credit-Card.php</link><category>Bad Credit / Credit Repair</category><description>Article addresses the question of having bad credit and needing a credit card.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Credit Repair: How to get back your credit</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/credit-repair-get-back-your-credit.php</link><category>Bad Credit / Credit Repair</category><description>Credit repair and the steps involved in using credit cards to improve your credit report and credit rating.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cleaning Up and Repairing Your Credit Rating</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/cleaning-up-and-repairing-your-credit.php</link><category>Bad Credit / Credit Repair</category><description>Methods for cleaning up and repairing your credit rating with credit cards and how using a credit card correctly can help build your credit history.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Repairing Credit Card Debt</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/credit-card-debt-article.php</link><category>Bad Credit / Credit Repair</category><description>Advice on repairing credit card debt including contacting creditors, dealing with debt collectors and debt counselors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Dispute Credit Report Errors</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/bad-credit-reports-article.php</link><category>Bad Credit / Credit Repair</category><description>Methods for how to dispute credit report errors including dealing with the three main credit bureaus, Equifax, Experian and Trans Union.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Good vs. Bad Credit: Why Is This Important?</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/good-vs-bad-credit.php</link><category>Bad Credit / Credit Repair</category><description>What is good vs. bad credit and why is this important - issues discussed involving debt consolidation for credit cards; how bad credit differs from good credit ratings and how credit card history affects credit reports with the three major credit bureaus.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Eufora Card is Worth a Look</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/The-Eufora-Card-is-Worth-a-Look</link><category>Bad Credit / Credit Repair</category><description>Detailed article on the Eufora Prepaid MasterCard credit card - a product option for those with no credit history, damaged credit, need to rebuild credit or establish credit with a credit bureau like Transunion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Compare Credit Card Options For Those With Bad Credit</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Comparing-Credit-Cards-for-Bad-Credit.php</link><category>Bad Credit / Credit Repair</category><description>An overview of how to compare credit card options for consumers with bad credit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Credit &amp; Consumer Rights</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/credit-consumer-rights-article.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>Detailed article on credit and consumer rights including how consumer credit rating, credit history, applications for credit and credit problems can affect their credit report and credit rating.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is a Credit Report?</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/what-is-a-credit-report.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>A review of what is a credit report and how use of credit cards impacts credit card APRs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Credit Reporting Q&amp;A</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/credit-reporting-q&amp;a.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>Credit reporting questions and answers reviewed involving credit cards, credit rating agencies, credit reporting and how this affects gaining access to credit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is a credit score and how does it affect me?</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/what-is-a-credit-score.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>An overview of what is a credit score and how does it affect me including an explanation of a credit report.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reviewing Your Credit Report Yearly</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Reviewing-Your-Credit-Report.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>Advice on reviewing your credit report yearly including checking for credit card payment behavior reported by issuers of credit cards on your credit report with Experian, Equifax and Trans Union.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Protecting Your Credit Card</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/protecting-your-credit-card.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>Article on protecting your credit cards - including your credit ranking, credit card information and personal credit card.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Do's and Don'ts of Closing Accounts</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/dos-and-donts.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>Article describing what you should and should not do when closing old accounts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Limiting Your Financial Loss</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/limiting-your-financial-loss.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>How to limit you financial loss if a credit card goes missing; report loss of credit cards, debit cards or ATM cards to issuing financial institution as soon a possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>What to Do When Credit Cards Are Lost or Stolen</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Credit-Cards-ATM-Cards-and-Debit-Cards.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>Article describing what to do when credit cards, ATM cards and debit cards are lost or stolen with advice on who to notify and when in order to limit financial liability for theft of credit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Privacy Options - How to Opt Out</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Credit-Card-Privacy-Options.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>Overview of credit card privacy options with the question how can I just opt-out, bank and credit card issuer privacy policy mailings often confused with junk mail.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Phishing - What it means and how to prevent it</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Phishing.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>Article describing what Phishing means and how consumers can prevent being a victim of identity when receiving emails or calls requesting personal information about a credit card, advice on online security precautions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Skimming - What it is and how to avoid being a victim</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Skimming.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>Article describing what skimming means and how avoid being a victim of identity fraud when using a credit card to shop or pay restaurant bills.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Online Account Management</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/online-account-management.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>Article discussing the methods for setting up online credit card account management processes to maximize rewards, cash back and miles on credit cards using recurring payments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Identity Theft - Protect Yourself with Watch-Guard</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/identity-theft-watch-guard-premier.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>Article on identity theft and how to protect yourself with Watch-Guard Premier from Citibank, service includes total wallet protection, identity theft protection, purchase protection and replacement of lost or stolen credit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cardmember Benefits - Visa Warranty Manager</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/cardmember-benefits-visa-warranty-manager.php</link><category>Credit / Account Management</category><description>Overview of cardmember benefits such as warranty protection (called warranty manager) that provides warranty extension or extended warranty protection for a visa credit card.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>How 0% APR credit cards can save you money</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/low-interest-credit-cards-article.php</link><category>Low Interest / 0% APR Cards</category><description>An explanation of why fixed low interest credit cards might be right for you and why credit card companies offer low introductory rates with a low interest rate on credit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saving on Interest Expenses with 0% APR Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Low-Interest-APR-Credit-Cards-Article543.php</link><category>Low Interest / 0% APR Cards</category><description>Methods for saving on interest expenses with low-interest and 0% APR credit cards involving paying off balances on time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>0% APR Credit Card Offers - Here to Stay or a Fad?</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/0-Credit-Card-Offers.php</link><category>Low Interest / 0% APR Cards</category><description>Learn what 0% APR credit card offers mean for consumers transferring balances and how temporary marketing gimmicks have become semi-permanent but may not last forever.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>After the Intro - Variable vs. Fixed Rate Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Variable-vs-Fixed-Rate-Credit-Cards.php</link><category>Low Interest / 0% APR Cards</category><description>After the intro period variable and fixed rate credit cards offer credit card customers go-to interest rates.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to use low APR credit cards to become debt free</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Using-Low-APR-Credit-Cards.php</link><category>Low Interest / 0% APR Cards</category><description>How to use 0% intro rate or low apr credit cards to become debt free.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>HSBC Has a Card for Every Occasion</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/HSBC-Has-a-Card-for-Every-Occasion.php</link><category>Low Interest / 0% APR Cards</category><description>HSBC has a card for everyone including those seeking a low interest 0% apr or reward credit card, including the GM Card.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eliminate Credit Card Debt</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Eliminate-Credit-Card-Debt.php</link><category>Balance Transfer / Debt Consolidation</category><description>Overview of U.S. personal debt, how to eliminate credit card debt, five steps to follow to become debt free, search for low interest and 0% APR credit card deals and lowest rate offers with our Balance Transfer Credit Cards section.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Comparing 0% Balance Transfer Offers</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Comparing-0-Balance-Transfer-Credit-Cards.php</link><category>Balance Transfer / Debt Consolidation</category><description>Comparing 0% Balance Transfer Credit Cards and finding the best credit card with low interest with which to transfer balances.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Credit Card Debt Consolidation</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/debt-consolidation-article.php</link><category>Balance Transfer / Debt Consolidation</category><description>CreditCards.com is a resource for consumers looking to apply for credit cards online.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Credit Card Debt</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/managing-and-getting-rid-of-debt.php</link><category>Balance Transfer / Debt Consolidation</category><description>Article detailing options for credit card debt consolidation through balance transfer credit card offers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transferring your way out of Credit Card Debt</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Credit-Card-Debt-Article821.php</link><category>Balance Transfer / Debt Consolidation</category><description>Methods for transferring your way out of credit card debt and how to transfer your balance to a lower interest credit card or one with a low introductory interest rate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Credit Card Consolidation</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Credit-Card-Consolidation.php</link><category>Balance Transfer / Debt Consolidation</category><description>Methods for credit card consolidation and how to save money in interest and finance charges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Credit card debt consolidation - Retire Those High Rate Plastics</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Credit-Card-Debt-Consolidation.php</link><category>Balance Transfer / Debt Consolidation</category><description>Advice on repairing credit card debt including contacting creditors, dealing with debt collectors and debt counselors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balance Transfers 101</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/balance-transfers-101.php</link><category>Balance Transfer / Debt Consolidation</category><description>Learn the steps involved that are critical to successfully performing a balance transfer of money owed from a high interest credit card to one that offers 0% APR, or at least a lower interest rate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Determine Which Reward Credit Card Is For You</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Which-Reward-Credit-Card-Is-Best.php</link><category>Reward Programs / Cash Back Cards</category><description>How to determine which reward credit card is best for you - overview of some of the best reward credit card programs chronology, types of reward credit cards described, points vs. cash back, no annual fee card examples including AT&amp;T Universal Card.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Super-size Your Credit Card Reward Program</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Credit-Card-Rewards-Programs.php</link><category>Reward Programs / Cash Back Cards</category><description>Examples of how to super-size your credit card rewards program, including ways to get extra value with a rewards credit card, with UPromise, online coupons and online shopping portals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maximize Your Reward Card Program</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Maximize-Your-Credit-Card-Rewards-Program.php</link><category>Reward Programs / Cash Back Cards</category><description>Leverage household and everyday spending to maximize your reward card program and how to leverage grocery, household bills, mortgage/rent, and other recurring payments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Cash Back Credit Cards Work</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/How-Cash-Back-Credit-Cards-Work.php</link><category>Reward Programs / Cash Back Cards</category><description>An explanation of how cash back credit cards work and an overview of flat and tiered earning rate structures for cash back credit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Compare Cash Back Credit Card Offers</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Comparing-Cash-Back-Credit-Card-Offers.php</link><category>Reward Programs / Cash Back Cards</category><description>How to Compare Cash back reward programs and how they may appear similar but differ in how they calculate rewards and how rewards are delivered.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cash Back vs. Reward Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Cash-Back-vs-Reward-Credit-Cards.php</link><category>Reward Programs / Cash Back Cards</category><description>Cash back and rewards credit card programs appear similar but differ in the type of rewards earned and how they are delivered.  To see the most competitive offers visit our Cash Back and Rewards Credit cards sections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cut Your Gas Bill with Gas Rebate Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Gas-Rebate-Credit-Cards.php</link><category>Reward Programs / Cash Back Cards</category><description>A review of how to cut your gas bill with gas rebate credit cards and how a gas rebate credit card works like a cash back credit card but shows how a gas rebate is applied to the cardholder statement each month unlike cashback cards with rebate checks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cash Back or Airline Reward Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Cash-Back-Airline-Reward-Credit-Cards.php</link><category>Reward Programs / Cash Back Cards</category><description>Cash back and airline reward credit cards - The benefits behind these two types of reward credit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gas Rebate Credit Cards - Looking Better All the Time</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/gas-rebate-credit-card.php</link><category>Reward Programs / Cash Back Cards</category><description>Article detailing the new Love the Double reward promotion by Chase Credit Card Services where cardholders of their credit cards can earn double rewards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Automobile Rebate Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/automobile-rebate-credit-cards.php</link><category>Reward Programs / Cash Back Cards</category><description>Article detailing with how to use automobile rebate credit cards to save on vehicle purchases and specific credit card offers including the GM Card, Volkswagen Platinum Visa, Subaru MasterCard and Citi Driver's Edge Card.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>So Many Rewards, So Little Time</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/so-many-rewards-so-little-time.php</link><category>Reward Programs / Cash Back Cards</category><description>So many rewards and so little time to earn them describes the situation with the multitude of credit card reward programs outlined, including cash back, reward and airline credit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strategies For Earning A Free Airline Ticket Sooner</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Earning-Frequent-Flyer-Credit-Card-Points.php</link><category>Airline / Frequent Flyer Programs</category><description>Methods for earning additional frequent flyer credit card miles from everyday purchases made with an airline rewards credit card, Citi AAdvantage MasterCard, Chase Value Miles Platinum Visa or rewards credit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Survey of Airline Rewards Programs</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Survey-of-Airline-Reward-Credit-Cards.php</link><category>Airline / Frequent Flyer Programs</category><description>A discussion and survey of frequent flyer and airline reward credit card options in the including the United Airlines, Chase Continental and Citi Advantage MasterCard Credit Card Programs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ's About Airline Frequent Flyer Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/FAQs-Airline-Credit-Cards.php</link><category>Airline / Frequent Flyer Programs</category><description>General questions and answers about airline frequent flyer rewards credit cards concerning fees, mileage earning and how to redeem for a free award ticket.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cash Back or Airline Reward Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Cash-Back-Airline-Reward-Credit-Cards.php</link><category>Airline / Frequent Flyer Programs</category><description>Cash back and airline reward credit cards - The benefits behind these two types of reward credit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Student Credit 101</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Student-Credit-Cards-101.php</link><category>Student Credit Card Education</category><description>Student credit cards 101 - basic information regarding how students can apply for and use their first credit card with a student credit card.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Comparing Student Credit Cards vs. Debit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Comparing-College-Student-Credit-Cards.php</link><category>Student Credit Card Education</category><description>Tips on how to compare the differences between college student credit cards and debit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Establish Credit with a Student Credit Card</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Establishing-Credit-With-A-Student-Credit-Card.php</link><category>Student Credit Card Education</category><description>Discussion how to establish with a student credit card and avoid credit card debt, the meaning and implications of building a credit rating and good credit score and how credit cards for students can help.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reasons For A Small Business Credit Card</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Reasons-For-A-Small-Business-Credit-Card.php</link><category>Credit Cards for Small Business</category><description>Listing and detail of reasons for a small business need a credit card, i.e. business credit card or corporate credit card for unsecured credit purposes to access capital with a low interest rate credit card.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using a Business Credit Card to Manage Expenses</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Using-Business-Credit-Card.php</link><category>Credit Cards for Small Business</category><description>Learn how to use A Business Credit Card for more than Frequent Flyer Airline Miles and Cash Back Incentives including controlling expenses with a low interest rate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Credit Cards for Small Business</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/credit-cards-for-small-business.php</link><category>Credit Cards for Small Business</category><description>Article on credit cards for small business, also known as a corporate credit card.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simplify Your Bookkeeping with a Corporate Credit Card</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Simplify-Your-Bookkeeping-Corporate-Credit-Card.php</link><category>Credit Cards for Small Business</category><description>Article on how to simplify your bookkeeping with a corporate credit card or small business credit card.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reward Options for Business Credit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Reward-Options-For-Business-Credit-Cards.php</link><category>Credit Cards for Small Business</category><description>Discussion of reward options for business credit cards involving frequent flyer miles, rewards and cash back programs through Visa, MasterCard, Discover Card and American Express.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Small Business Credit Cards Differ from Corporate Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/small-business-corporate-card.php</link><category>Credit Cards for Small Business</category><description>An explanation of how small business credit cards are different than corporate credit cards and other types of business credit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Advanta Means Business</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Advanta-Means-Business.php</link><category>Credit Cards for Small Business</category><description>Article describing how Advanta means business with its business credit card selection featured on creditcards.com, including the advanta platinum business card with 0% apr and cash back rewards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are The Pro's and Con's of Prepaid Debit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Pros-and-Cons-of-Prepaid-Debit-Cards.php</link><category>Prepaid / Debit Cards</category><description>A discussion of what are the pro's and con's of prepaid debit cards comparing credit card, secured credit card, debit card and prepaid debit card options from the major issuers of credit cards such as Visa and MasterCard.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Technology Features Offered for Prepaid Debit Cards</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/New-Technology-For-Prepaid-Debit-Cards.php</link><category>Prepaid / Debit Cards</category><description>Discussion of new technology features offered for prepaid debit cards relative to credit cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Do Prepaid Debit Cards Differ</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/How-Do-Prepaid-Debit-Cards-Differ.php</link><category>Prepaid / Debit Cards</category><description>Discussion of differences between prepaid debit cards, bank debit cards and bank ATM cards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pay in the Blink of an Eye with the Chase Blink Card</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Pay-in-the-Blink-of-an-Eye.php</link><category>News About Credit Cards</category><description>A new credit card innovation has arrived which will make going through the check out line a little faster for Chase cardholders.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Bankruptcy Law - What Does it all Mean?</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/The-New-Bankruptcy-Law.php</link><category>News About Credit Cards</category><description>The new bankruptcy law that was passed by congress and signed by the President will go into effect on October 17, 2005. But what does it mean to consumers?</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>Earn 5% Cash Back with Discover</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Earn-Cash-Back-with-Discover.php</link><category>News About Credit Cards</category><description>Overview of how to earn 5% cash back with a discover credit card through their cash back bonus program.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Chase Love the Double Promotion Could Have You Seeing Double</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/The-New-Chase-Love-the-Double-Promotion-Could-Have-You-Seeing-Double.php</link><category>News About Credit Cards</category><description>Article detailing the new Love the Double reward promotion by Chase Credit Card Services where cardholders of their credit cards can earn double rewards.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item><item><title>JetBlue and American Express launch new card - September 12, 2005</title><link>http://www.creditcards.com/Jetblue-American-Express-Credit-Card.php</link><category>News About Credit Cards</category><description>An exciting new frequent flyer credit card issued in partnership with American Express. The card will allow customers to earn free tickets on Jet Blue Airlines even faster.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2005 09:45:25 CDT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
